(Sheldon:)So, what
brings you by?
Well,
(Howard:)I don't need a reason--
it's my house.
(Stuart:)Technically,
it's your mom's house, but...
(Stuart:)we certainly want you
to feel welcome.
(Howard:)I'm always welcome.
(Stuart:)Mm, just... try and call first.
(Bernadette:)Okay, let's get
down to business.
(Bernadette:)Howie was thinking about
putting up some money
(Bernadette:)to help you reopen the store,
but before that happens,
(Bernadette:)I have a few questions.
Oh.
(Stuart:)I appreciate the offer,
(Stuart:)but actually your mother
already gave me the money.
(Howard:)What?
(Stuart:)Yeah. I told her
it was too much,
(Stuart:)but she said she was happy
to help out her bubala.
(chuckles)
(Raj:)Excuse me.
Ma, you are canceling
that check,
and Stuart is not your bubala;
I'm your bubala.
(Howard:)You can't have more
than one bubala!
(Penny:)I don't know
who he's talking to.
(Stuart:)She's at Target,
buying me shirts.